https://www.woofish.com/privacy/

Skip to content
HomeFishingAccessoriesLinesReelsRodsPrivacy PolicyDisclaimerContactsPrivacy PolicyLast updated: October 13, 2019 WooFish.com (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the WooFish.com website (the “Service”).This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use
and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.We
use your Personal Information for providing and improving the
Service.
By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of
information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in
this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same
meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at
WooFish.com.Information Collection And UseWhile
using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally
identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you.
Personally identifiable information (“Personal
Information”) may
include, but is not limited to:Email addressLog DataWe
collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our
Service (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your
computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser
version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of
your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.Amazon, Google AdSense & DoubleClick CookieGoogle and Amazon as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Service.CookiesCookies
are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous
unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web
site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.We use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your
browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being
sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use
some portions of our Service.Service ProvidersWe
may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our
Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform
Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is
used.These third parties have access to your Personal
Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated
not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.SecurityThe
security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember
that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of
electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially
acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot
guarantee its absolute security.Links To Other SitesOur
Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If
you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third
party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of
every site you visit.We have no control over,and assume no responsibility for the content,
privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.Children’s PrivacyOur Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”).We
do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from
children under 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware
that your child has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us.
If we discover that a child under 18 has provided us with
Personal
Information, we will delete such information from our servers
immediately.Compliance With LawsWe will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena.Changes To This Privacy PolicyWe
may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of
any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.You
are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.
Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on
this page.Contact UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.Affiliate DisclosureWe are a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com, Amazon.co.uk, Amazon.deLatest Posts Best Boot Dryers Best Trolling Motors Best Fishing Lines Best Tackle Boxes Best Fish Finders Under $200CategoriesAccessoriesFishingLinesReelsRodsFollow us
HomeFishingAccessoriesLinesReelsRodsPrivacy PolicyDisclaimerContacts
Close
